Joey Bishop papers
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Joey Bishop Show Records.
  - Guest Research Files.
    - Kean, Bettie & Parker, Lew., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kean, Jane., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Kellogg, Lynn., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kelly, Barbara., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Kelly, Emmett., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kennedy, George., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kennedy, Senator Robert., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Kerr, Dick., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kershaw, Doug., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kiley, Richard., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Kim Sisters., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kim, Andy., 1969. (Box 12)
    - King Sisters., 1969. (Box 12)
    - King, Morgana., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kirby, George., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kitt, Eartha., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Klein, Robert., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kneivel, Evil., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Knight, Gladys and The Pips., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Knotts, Don., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kover, Kitty 1 of 2., 1968. (Box 12)
      Scope and Contents note
      With audio recording labeled Kitty Kover; (7.5 inch reel tape).
      RESTRICTED FROM ACCESS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    - Krause, Patricia., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Kreig, Margaret., undated. (Box 12)
    - Kreski, Connie., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Kreskin., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Krofft, Sid & Marty., undated. (Box 12)
    - Kuda-Bux (Kooda-Bucks)., 1969. (Box 12)
    - L., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Laine, Frankie., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Lamas, Fernando., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lamour, Dorothy., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Lancaster, Burt., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Lanchester, Elsa., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Lane, Abbe., 1969. (Box 12)
    - Lane, Mark., 1968. (Box 12)
    - Langdon, Sue Ane., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lange, Hope., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lanning, Jerry., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Laver, Rod., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lawford, Peter., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lawrence, Carol., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Layne, John., 1967. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Berri., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Brenda., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Dal Joon/ Jack Howard., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Gypsy Rose., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lee, London., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Michele., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lee, Peggy., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Legrand, Michel., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Leigh, Janet., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lemmon, Jack., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lennon Sisters., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Leonard, Jack E.., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Leonetti, Tommy., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lessey, Ben., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lester, Ketty., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Letta., 1969. (Box 13)
    - The Lettermen., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Gary & The Playboys., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Jerry Lee., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Ramsey., undated. (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Shari., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lewis, Ted., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lindsey, George., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Linkletter, Art., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Linn, Roberta., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lisi, Virna., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Little Dion., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Little, Big Tiny., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Little, Rich., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Locke, Sondra., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lockhart, June., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lolich, Mickey and the Four Scores., 1968. (Box 13)
    - London, Julie and the Bobby Troup., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Loring, Gloria., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Loy, Myrna., 1968. (Box 13)
    - Lulu., 1969. (Box 13)
    - Lundberg, Victor., 1967. (Box 14)
    - Lupino, Ida., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Lynn, Judy., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Mabley, Moms., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Mackenzie, Gisele., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Macnee, Patrick., 1968. (Box 14)
    - MacRae, Gordon., 1969. (Box 14)
    - MacRae, Meredith., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Makeba, Miriam., 1968. (Box 14)
    - Malden, Karl., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Maltese Bippy., undated. (Box 14)
    - Manna, Charlie., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Mantle, Mickey., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Manuela., 1968. (Box 14)
    - Marandi, Evi., undated. (Box 14)
    - Marceau, Marcel., 1968. (Box 14)
    - Marciano, Rocky., 1968. (Box 14)
    - Mardo, Al., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Marks, Guy., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martha and the Vandellas., undated. (Box 23)
    - Marr, Jamie., 1968. (Box 14)
    - Marshal, E.G.., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Bobbi., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Dino Jr.., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Gail., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Ronnie., undated. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Ross., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Martin, Steve., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Martin, Tony., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Martino, Al., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Marvin, Lee., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Marx, Groucho., undated. (Box 15)
    - Masekela, Hugh., 1967. (Box 15)
    - Mason, Jackie., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mason, James., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mason, Jana., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mason, Pamela., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mason, Pamela., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Massey, Daniel., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mataalii, Tigi., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mathis, Johnny., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Matthau, Walter (& Jack Lemmon)., 1968. (Box 15)
    - May, Marilyn., 1969. (Box 15)
    - McCall, Mitzi and Brill, Charlie., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McCarthy, Senator Eugene., 1968. (Box 14)
    - McClure, Doug., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McCrea, Joel., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McDowall, Roddy., 1968. (Box 14)
    - McGavin, Darren., 1968. (Box 14)
    - McGuire, Phyllis., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McKay, Jim., 1968. (Box 14)
    - McKay, John (Coach)., undated. (Box 14)
    - McKuen, Rod., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McLain, Denny., 1968. (Box 14)
    - McNair, Barbara., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McRae, Carmen., 1969. (Box 14)
    - McRae, Sheila., 1969. (Box 14)
    - Medley, Bill., 1969. (Box 15)
      With 45 rpm record.
    - Melvin, Bob., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mendes, Sergio & Brasil., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mercouri, Melina., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Merman, Ethel., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Merrill, Robert., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mesta, Perle., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Meza, Lee., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Michaels, Marilyn., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mickey Mouse., undated. (Box 15)
    - Miller, Ann., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Miller, Cheryl., 1967. (Box 15)
    - Miller, Jody., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Miller, Roger., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mills Brothers., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mineo, Sal., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Minnelli, Liza., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Minnesota Fats., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Minnie Pearl., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Minter, Don., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mintz, Elliot., 1968-1969. (Box 15)
    - The Mission., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mitchell, Chad., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mitchell, Joni., 1968. (Box 15)
    - Mitchell, Willie., 1969. (Box 15)
    - Mitchilll, Scoey., 1969. (Box 15)
    - M-Mc., 1968. (Box 14)
    - The Mob., 1969. (Box 16)
    - The Modern Aires., undated. (Box 16)
    - Monica, Corbett., 1968. (Box 16)
    - The Monkees., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Monro, Matt., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Montalban, Ricardo., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Montevecchi, Liliane., undated. (Box 16)
    - Montgomery, George., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Montgomery, Wes., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Moorehead, Agnes., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Morgan, Jane., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Morita, Pat., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Morse, Bobby., undated. (Box 16)
    - Mothers of Invention., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Muhammad Ali (Cassius Clay)., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Murad, Jerry & Harmonicats., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Jimmy & Anne., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Murray, Don., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Murray, Jan., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Murray, Ken., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Muskie, Edmund S.., 1968. (Box 16)
    - N., 1967-1968. (Box 16)
    - Nabors, Jim., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Namath, Joe., no date. (Box 16)
    - Neglia, Maria., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Ozzie and Harriet., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Rick., 1969. (Box 16)
    - The New Christy Minstrels., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Newley, Anthony., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Newton, Wayne., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Nicklaus, Jack., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Nidetch, Jean., 1967. (Box 16)
    - Nimoy, Leonard., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Nixon, Marni., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Nixon, Richard M.., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Nizer, Louie., 1968. (Box 16)
    - Norris, Chuck., 1969. (Box 16)
    - Novarro, Ramon., no date. (Box 16)
    - Nye, Lewis., 1969. (Box 16)
    - O., 1968. (Box 16)
    - O'Brian, Hugh., 1968. (Box 16)
    - O'Brien, Pat., 1969. (Box 17)
    - O'Byrne, Maria., 1968. (Box 17)
    - O'Connell, Helen., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Odetta., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Ofareem, Esther & Abi., 1968. (Box 17)
    - O'Hara, Maureen., undated. (Box 17)
    - Oliver., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Oliver, Susan., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Omarr, Sydney., 1969. (Box 17)
    - O'Neal, Ryan., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Osborne, Mary., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Oscar., undated. (Box 17)
    - Osmond, The Brothers., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Owens, Buck., 1969. (Box 17)
    - P Q., 1968-1969. (Box 17)
    - Pace, Frank., 1967. (Box 17)
    - Paige, Janis., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Pair Extraordinaire., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Palance, Jack., undated. (Box 17)
    - Palmer, Arnold., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Paris, Freddie., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Parker, Fess., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Patchett & Tarsus., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Paulsen, Pat., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Peaker, E.J.., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Pearce Sisters., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Peerce, Jan., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Peiro Brothers., 1969. (Box 17)
    - People Tree., undated. (Box 17)
    - Peppermint Rainbow., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Persoff, Nehemiah., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Peterson, Monica., 1968. (Box 17)
    - Peterson, Oscar., 1969. (Box 17)
    - Photoplay Awards., 1967-1968. (Box 17)
    - Piazza, Marguerite., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Picardi, Angelo., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Piccola Pupa., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Pickle Brothers., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Picon, Molly., undated. (Box 18)
      With book titled So Laugh A Little by Molly Picon.
    - Piersall, Jimmy., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Pike, Very Rev. James A.., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Poco., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Pope, Ralph., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Porter, Robie., 1969. (Box 18)
    - The Potpourri., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Pozo-Seco Singers., undated. (Box 18)
    - Preminger, Otto., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Preston, Billy., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Price, Gilbert., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Price, Vincent., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Pride, Charley., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Prowse, Juliet., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Pryor, Richard., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Quarry, Jerry., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Quinn, Anthony., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Quinn, Anthony., 1969. (Box 18)
    - R., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Rabin, Michael., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Raisch, Bill., undated. (Box 18)
    - Ramsen, Bobby., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Randall, Frankie., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Randolph, Boots., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Ranji., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Rawls, Lou., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Ray, Anita & Hall, Diane., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Ray, Johnnie., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Raye, Martha., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Reagan, Nancy., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Redwing, Rodd., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Reed, Jerry., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Reed, Rex., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Reese, Della., 1969. (Box 18)
    - Reiner, Carl., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Rey, Alejandro., 1968. (Box 18)
    - Reynolds, Debbie., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Reynolds, Frank., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Rice, Don., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Rich, Buddy., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Richards, Ann., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Rickles, Don., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Righteous Brothers., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Righter, Carroll., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Riley, Jeannie C.., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Ritchard, Cyril., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Ritz Brothers., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rivera, Chita., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Robbins, Marty., undated. (Box 19)
    - Roberts, Judy., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Roberts, Pernell., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Robertson, Cliff., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Robertson, Dale., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Robin, Tina., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Robinson, Sugar Ray., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rockwell, Norman., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Rodgers, Jimmie., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Roe, Tommy., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rogers, Roy & Dale., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rogers, Timmy., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Roman, Dick., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Roman, Lyn., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Romano, D'Aldo., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Romero, Cesar., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Ronstadt, Linda., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rooney, Mickey., 1969. (Box 19)
      With book titled I.E. An Autobiography by Mickey Rooney.
    - Rose, Marie., undated. (Box 19)
    - Ross, Barbara., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Ross, Joe E.., 1968. (Box 19)
    - Rouvaun., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rowan and Martin., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Royal Guardsmen., undated. (Box 19)
    - The Royal Quartet., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rush, Merilee., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Russell, Bill., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Russell, Bobby., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Russell, Nipsey., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Rydell, Bobby., 1968. (Box 19)
    - S., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Sahl, Mort., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Saint James, Susan., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sainte-Marie, Buffy., undated. (Box 20)
    - Salinger, Pierre., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sandi and Sally., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sandler and Young., 1969. (Box 20)
    - The Sandpipers., undated. (Box 20)
    - Sands, Evie., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sands, Sonny., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Saridis, Saverio., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Savalas, Telly., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Schell, Maximillian., undated. (Box 20)
    - Schell, Ronnie., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Scott, George C.., undated. (Box 20)
    - Scott, Hazel., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Scotti, Tony., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Scully, Vin., 1969. (Box 20)
    - The Seeds., undated. (Box 20)
    - Sennes, Sandra., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Shane, Jerry., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shango., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shankar, Ravi., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Sharif, Omar., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Shatner, William., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Shaughnessy, Mickey., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shawn, Dick., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shearing, George., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sheldon, Gene., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shepard and Jourdan., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sherman, Allan., 1967, 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sherman, Bobby., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Sherwood, Roberta., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Shore, Dinah., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Shore, Sammy., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sifford, Charlie., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Silvers, Phil., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Simmons, Jean., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Simpson, O.J.., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Sinatra, Frank Jr.., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Skiles & Henderson., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Skolsky, Sidney., 1968. (Box 20)
    - Smith, Glenn & The Fables., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Smith, Howlett., 1969. (Box 20)
    - Smith, Jimmy., undated. (Box 21)
    - Smith, Keely., 1967. (Box 21)
    - Smith, O.C.., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Smith, Rev. A. Kendall., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Smith, Roger and Ann Margaret., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Smokey Robinson & the Miracles., 1969. (Box 19)
    - Smothers, Tommy & Dick., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Snyder, Councilman Arthur K., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Sommer, Elke., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Sommers, Joanie., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Son of a Gun Players., undated. (Box 21)
    - Sonny and Cher., 1969. (Box 21)
    - The Soul Survivors., undated. (Box 21)
    - South, Joe., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Spanky & Our Gang., 1968. (Box 21)
    - The Spiral Starecase., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Springfield, Dusty., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stack, Robert., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stamp, Terrence., 1968. (Box 21)
    - The Standells., no date. (Box 21)
    - STAR Premiere., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Starr, Kay., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Statler Brothers., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Steele, Tommy., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Steiger, Rod., undated. (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Connie., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Dodie., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Kaye., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Ray., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stevens, Stella., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Stewart, Jackie., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stewart, John., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stone Brook People., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stone, Elly., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Stone, Harvey., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Storch, Larry., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Strand, Tommy & the Upper Hand., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Strasberg, Susan., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Strawberry Alarm Clock., undated. (Box 21)
    - Styles, Herkie., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Sullivan, Barry., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Sunday's Child., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Sunshine Co.., undated. (Box 21)
    - Susann, Jacqueline., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Swanson, Gloria., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Sweet Charity., 1969. (Box 21)
    - Syms, Sylvia., 1968. (Box 21)
    - Tapp, Demetriss., 1968. (Box 22)
    - The Tartans., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Taylor, Bill., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Taylor, Cathie., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Taylor, George S.., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Taylor, Mary., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Taylor, Rip., 1969. (Box 22)
    - The Temptations., undated. (Box 22)
    - Tex, Joe., undated. (Box 22)
    - Thaxton, Lloyd., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Theodore, Brother., undated. (Box 22)
    - Thinnes, Roy., undated. (Box 22)
    - Thomas, Bob., undated. (Box 22)
    - Thomas, Danny., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Thomas, Marlo., undated. (Box 22)
    - Thomas, Terre., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Thomas, Terry., 1967. (Box 22)
    - Thompson, Hank., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Thompson, Kay., undated. (Box 22)
    - Three Dog Night., 1969. (Box 22)
    - The Three Stooges., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Tibbs, Casey., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Tillotson, Johnny., 1969. (Box 22)
    - The Times Square Two., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Todd, Mike Jr.., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Tommy James and the Shondells., undated. (Box 20)
    - Toomey, Bill., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Torme, Mel., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Tors, Ivan., 1968. (Box 22)
    - The Toys., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Trask, Diana., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Trenier, Milt & Micki Lynn., 1967. (Box 22)
    - Trevor, Claire., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Tucker, Forrest., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Tucker, Richard., 1967. (Box 22)
    - Tufts, Sonny., undated. (Box 22)
    - Tunney, John V.., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Turner, Ike & Tina., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Uggams, Leslie., 1969. (Box 22)
    - United States Navy Precision Drill Team., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Unruh, Speaker Jesse., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Unser, Bobby., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Vale, Jerry., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Valenti, Caterina., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Valenti, Jack., undated. (Box 22)
    - Valery, Dana., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Valli, Frankie., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Van & Palmer., 1969. (Box 22)
    - Van Buren, Abigail., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Van Doren, Mamie., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Van Dyke, Jerry., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Van Dyke, LeRoy., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Van Patten, Joyce., undated. (Box 23)
    - Van, Bobby., 1968. (Box 22)
    - Vanilla Fudge., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Vaugh, Father Tom., undated. (Box 23)
    - Vaughan, Sarah., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Vaughn, Robert., undated. (Box 23)
    - Vee, Bobby., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Ver Planck, Marlene., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Verdon, Gwen., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Veregge, Dr. Gerald., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Vernon, Jackie., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Vernon, Jeremy., undated. (Box 23)
    - Vignon, Jean Paul., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Villa, Joey., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Vinton, Bobby., 1969. (Box 23)
    - W., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Wade, Adam., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Wagner, Robert., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Wagner, Roger., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Walden, Lois., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Walker, Betty., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Wallace, Governor George C.., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Walley, Deborah., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Wallis, Shani., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Walter, Jessica., undated. (Box 23)
    - Walton, Sunni., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Wanderley, Walter., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Ward, Clara., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Warren, Ivan., 1969. (Box 23)
    - Watson, David., 1968. (Box 23)
    - Watts 103 Street Rhythm Band., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wayne, John., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wayne, Paula., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Weaver, Dennis., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Welch, Raquel., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Welk, Lawrence., 1969. (Box 24)
      With The Champagne Music of Lawrence Welk calendar.
    - Welles, Orson., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Werle, Barbara., undated. (Box 24)
    - Wesley, Ltn. Don., undated. (Box 24)
    - Weston, Kim., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Whaler Girls., 1968. (Box 24)
    - White, Tony Joe., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Whiting, Margaret., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Whitney, Marva., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wilkinson, June., 1969. (Box 24)
    - William, Andy., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Williams, Hank Jr.., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Williams, Joe., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Williams, Roger., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Earl Jr.., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Flip., no dateundated. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Jackie., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Marie., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Nancy., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wilson, Robin., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Winchell, Paul., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Winters, Shelly., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Woodbury, Woody., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Woods, Bret., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Woodward, Joanne., 1968. (Box 24)
    - World Action Singers., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Wrightson, Earl and Hunt, Lois., undated. (Box 24)
    - Wyman, Jane., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Wynette, Tammy., 1969. (Box 24)
    - York, Susannah., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Yorty, Sam (Mayor)., undated. (Box 24)
    - Young Holt Unlimited., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Young Rascals., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Young, Donna Jean., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Young, Gig., 1968. (Box 24)
    - Young, Leigh Taylor., 1968-1969. (Box 24)
    - Young, Otis., undated. (Box 24)
    - Young, Robert., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Younger, Evelle (D.A.)., undated. (Box 24)
    - Youngman, Henny., 1969. (Box 24)
    - Zimbalist, Efrem, Jr.., 1969. (Box 24)
  - Joey Bishop Show Weekly Line-Up.
    - Show(s) 1-25., 1967 Apr 17 - May 19. (Box 25)
    - Show(s) 26-53., 1967 May 22 - June 28. (Box 26)
    - Show(s) 54-83., 1967 June 9 - Aug 10. (Box 27)
    - Show(s) 84-93., 1967 Aug 11 - Aug 24. (Box 28)
    - Show(s) 95-112., 1967 Aug 25 - Sept 19. (Box 28)
    - Show(s) 113-115., 1967 Sept 20 - Sept 22. (Box 29)
    - Show(s) 131-155., 1967 Oct 23 - Nov 17. (Box 29)
    - Show(s) 156 - 185., 1967 Nov 20 - Dec 29. (Box 30)
    - Show(s) 186-215., 1968 Jan 1 - Feb 9. (Box 31)
    - Show(s) 216-249., 1968 Feb 12 - Mar 28. (Box 32)
    - Show(s) 250-255., 1968 Mar 29 - Apr 5. (Box 33)
    - Show(s) 257., 1968 Apr 9. (Box 33)
    - Show(s) 259-286., 1968 Apr 11 - May 20. (Box 33)
    - Show(s) 287-299., 1968 May 21 - June 5. (Box 34)
    - Show(s) 301-324., 1968 June 7 - July 11. (Box 34)
    - Show(s) 325-339., 1968 July 12 - Aug 1. (Box 35)
    - Show(s) 341-358., 1968 Aug 5 - Aug 28. (Box 35)
    - Show(s) 360-365., 1968 Aug 30 - Sept 6. (Box 35)
    - Show(s) 366-396., 1968 Sept 9 - Oct 21. (Box 36)
    - Show(s) 398-406., 1968 Oct 23 - Nov 4. (Box 36)
    - Show(s) 408-409., 1968 Nov 6 - Nov 7. (Box 36)
    - Show(s) 410-441., 1968 Nov 8 - Dec 23. (Box 37)
    - Show(s) 444-455., 1968 Dec 26 - 1969 Jan 10. (Box 37)
    - Show(s) 456-497., 1969 Jan 13 - Mar 11. (Box 38)
    - Show(s) 498-536., 1969 Mar 12 - May 6. (Box 39)
    - Show(s) 537-567., 1969 May 7 - June 19. (Box 40)
    - Show(s) 568-599., 1969 June 20 - Aug 5. (Box 41)
    - Show(s) 600-608., 1969 Aug 6 - Aug 18. (Box 42)
    - Show(s) 610-637., 1969 Aug 20 - Sept 26. (Box 42)
    - Show(s) 638-672., 1969 Sept 29 - Nov 14. (Box 43)
    - Show(s) 673-702., 1969 Nov 17 - Dec 26. (Box 44)
- Television Projects.
  The series consists of scripts documenting Bishop’s appearances on a variety of popular television programs such as Chico and the Man (1976), The Dean Martin Show (1971, 1972), The Don Rickles Show (1968), The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour (1969, 1971), Rowan and Martin’s Laugh-In (1968, 1970), and the Sonny and Cher Show (1971). Additionally there is script for the Seven Year Itch (undated).
  - Chico and the Man: Too Many Crooks - final draft script and binder., 1976 Jan 22. (Box 44)
  - The Dean Martin Show - final draft script and binder., 1971 Nov 24. (Box 44)
  - The Dean Martin Show - final draft script and binder., 1972 Aug 2. (Box 44)
  - The Don Rickles Show - script (with binder)., 1968. (Box 45)
  - The Glen Campbell Goodtime Hour - final draft script and log run down and binder., 1969 Feb 23. (Box 45)